Guide to the Jacob Harvey Family Papers 1811-1994 MS 306
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Harvey Family Papers, 1808-1950; 3.75 Linear feet
  - Subseries II.C. Mary Hosack Harvey Correspondence and Scrapbook, 1810-1950; 0.53 Linear feet
    Letters to Mary Hosack Harvey during the illness and upon the death of Jacob Harvey are situated at the beginning of the subseries. Following these, correspondents represented by several letters, or who are especially notable, are arranged alphabetically and foldered by surname. Correspondents represented by three or fewer letters are foldered together.
    The Feinses appear to have flattened and labeled a portion of these letters using paper sleeves. The sleeves have been left in place, although the order imposed by the Feinses has been disrupted significantly.
    - Letters to Mary Hosack Harvey During the Illness & on the Death of Jacob Harvey, 1848 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 1)
      Includes one letter each addressed to Abraham Bell and to Dr. Hosack (presumably Alexander Eddy).
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from B. Binsse, 1828 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 2)
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from Robert Greenhow, 1819-1822 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 3)
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from Mary Harvey, 1851-1852, Undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 4)
      Includes one letter from Mary Harvey to Rebecca Harvey which had been enclosed in a letter from Mary Harvey to Mary Hosack Harvey on July 16.
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from Mary C. Harvey, 1848 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 5)
      Letters of condolence on the death of Jacob Harvey. Includes one letter from Mary C. Harvey to Mary and Rebecca Harvey, and one letter from Hannah C. Harvey (Hannah H. Todhunter) to Mary Hosack Harvey, both of which accompanied the letter from Mary C. Harvey to Mary Hosack Harvey.
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from Rebecca Harvey, 1852, Undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 6)
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from William Henry Harvey (1 of 9), 1848-1849 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 7)
      Includes one letter from William Henry Harvey to J.A. Lowell, which had been enclosed in a letter from W.H. Harvey to Mary Hosack Harvey on 22 March 1849, concerning a trip to the United States (August 1849-May 1850) and a lecture course on botany, to be given by W.H. Harvey, at the Lowell institute near Boston, MA. Correspondence in this folder and the following two folders is predominantly concerned with W.H. Harvey's work and his trip to America.
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from William Henry Harvey (2 of 9), 1849 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 8)
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from William Henry Harvey (3 of 9), 1850 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 9)
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from William Henry Harvey (4 of 9), 1850 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 10)
      Includes two letters from Hannah Harvey Todhunter to Mary Hosack Harvey which was written on the back of W.H. Harvey's letter to Mary H. Harvey on 17 July 1850, and on 28 November 1850.
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from William Henry Harvey (5 of 9), 1851 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 11)
      Includes one letter from R. Harvey to William Henry Harvey which had been enclosed in a letter from W.H. Harvey to Mary Hosack Harvey on 13 March 1851, and one empty envelope.
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from William Henry Harvey (6 of 9), 1852 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 12)
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from William Henry Harvey (7 of 9), 1857 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 13)
      Includes one letter from R.H.T. (Todhunter) to Mary H. Harvey which was included in a letter from W.H. Harvey to M.H. Harvey on 19 March 1857.
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from William Henry Harvey (8 of 9), 1858 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 14)
      Includes one letter from Mary C. Harvey to "Darling Mother" which had been included in a letter from William Henry Harvey to Mary Hosack Harvey on 15 April 1858, concerning the death of Mary C. Harvey.
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from William Henry Harvey (9 of 9), 1859-1865 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 15)
    - Mary Hosack Harvey to/from Alexander Eddy Hosack & Celine B. Scott, 1857-1869 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 16)
      Includes a carte de visite depicting Alexander E. Hosack and a letter from Mary H. Harvey to Alexander E. Hosack which had, as a result of a quarrel, been returned unopened to Mary H. Harvey.
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from Emily Hosack & Nathaniel Pendleton Hosack, 1857-1869 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 17)
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from Rodgers Family, 1871 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 18)
      One letter from Emily Rodgers (Emmie) concerning a trip to Switzerland.
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from Schermerhorn Family, 1852-1855, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 19)
      Correspondents include: Adeline Schermerhorn (née Adeline E. Coster) (1825, undated); Ellen Schermerhorn (1855, undated).
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from Hannah Harvey Todhunter, 1856, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 20)
    - Mary Hosack Harvey to Mrs. Williams, 1836 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 21)
    - Mary Hosack Harvey from Correspondents B-T, 1812-1835, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 22)
      Correspondents include: S. Bard (1828, undated); Julia Bush (1812); Charles Choisy (1835); Maria Colden (1833); Louise Fai-- (undated); Mrs. Oakey (1863); D. Stewart (1814-1821); M. Toland (1824).
    - Poetry to Mary Hosack from Admirers, 1821, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1835 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 24)
      Obituary notices of the death of David Hosack.
    - Scrap Book Belonging to Mary Hosack Harvey (1 of 3), 1813-1822, undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 1)
    - Scrap Book Belonging to Mary Hosack Harvey (2 of 3), 1810-1849, undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 2)
      Miscellaneous loose scraps from the scrapbook, including newspaper clippings, engravings, and handwritten notes.
    - Scrap Book Belonging to Mary Hosack Harvey (3 of 3), 1950 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 3)
      Envelope, addressed to Mrs. Clare Feins, from Miss Constance Biddle, in which the scrapbook had been stored.
  - Subseries II.D. Mary Harvey Correspondence, 1839-1888; 0.33 Linear feet
    This subseries contains the correspondence of Mary Harvey, daughter of Mary H. and Jacob Harvey, written between the years 1839 and 1888. Letters from her family comprise a significant portion of the correspondence, and she received letters from her mother, Mary H. Harvey, her sister, Rebecca Harvey, her aunts and uncle Eliza, Sophia, and Nathaniel Hosack, as well as from Emily Hosack Rodgers and her daughters. She also received letters from her relatives in Ireland, including Mary C. Harvey, J.I. Harvey, William Henry Harvey, and Hannah H. and J. Todhunter. Correspondence, family and otherwise, is generally concerned with life and society in New York and in Ireland. Correspondents frequently reference one another, and their letters document significant events such as marriages, illnesses, and deaths, in addition to common social events, country retreats, and trips around the United States and Europe.
    The subseries is arranged alphabetically by correspondent. Correspondents represented by several letters, or who are especially notable, are foldered individually by surname. Correspondents represented by three or fewer letters are foldered together at the end of the subseries.
    - Mary Harvey from Anne C. Cary, 1851-1861 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 4)
    - Mary Harvey from Julia L. Delafield, 1855-1861 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 5)
    - Mary Harvey from J. I. Harvey, 1865 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 6)
    - Mary Harvey from Mary C. Harvey, 1848-1857 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 7)
    - Mary Harvey from Mary Hosack Harvey, 1839-1869 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 8)
      Includes one letter from M. Bell (Mary) to Mary Harvey (1848).
    - Mary Harvey from Rebecca Harvey, 1852-1857 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 9)
    - Mary Harvey from William Henry Harvey, 1850-1863 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 10)
      Includes a letter from Hannah H. Todhunter to Mary Harvey which was enclosed with a letter from W.H. Harvey to Mary Harvey on 26 May 1853, as well as two empty envelopes (1851 & 1854).
    - Mary Harvey from Hosack Family, 1852-1857 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 11)
      Correspondents include: Eliza Bard Hosack (1852); Nathaniel Pendleton Hosack (1858); Sophia Hosack (1859).
    - Mary Harvey from Julia James, 1853-1861, undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 12)
    - Mary Harvey from Julia Lowndes, 1848-1856 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 13)
    - Mary Harvey from Anne Stuart Newton, 1857-1859 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 14)
      The letters in this folder appear to be from a single correspondent, Anne Stuart Newton. There are, however, some inconsistencies in the signatures, and it is possible that the letters are from more than one correspondent with the same last name.
    - Mary Harvey from Rodgers Family, 1850-1888 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 15)
      Correspondents include: Ellen L. Newman (1888); -- O'Sullivan (1887); Emily Hosack Rodgers (Aunt Em) (1861); Emily Kearney Rodgers (Emmie) (1857-1859); Kit Rodgers (1850); Mary Hosack Biddle (Minni) (née Mary Hosack Rodgers) (1857-1888, undated).
    - Mary Harvey from Schermerhorn Family, 1852-1861, undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 16)
      Correspondents include: Adeline Schermerhorn (Aunt Addie) (1848-1861); Ellen Schermerhorn (1852-1861, undated).
    - Mary Harvey from Sarah Morris Stout (Sarah Morris Vaugrigneuse), 1854-1861 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 1)
      Includes, among a number of letters, one empty envelope (1857).
    - Mary Harvey from J. Todhunter, 1858 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 2)
    - Mary Harvey from Wilkes Family, 1852-1859 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 3)
      Correspondents include: Annie Wilkes (1852-1857); Grace Wilkes (1859); Hatty K. Wilkes (?) (1855-1859).
    - Mary Harvey from Correspondents E-T, 1852-1861 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 4)
      Correspondents include: Mary Edgar (1857); Katharine Ehninger (1853); Jon Ford (1855); A. Frenfanelli (1858-1859); S. A. Plan-- (1857); Fanny Rhinelander (1857); Helen Skinner (1857-1859); Julia Tillon (1859); H. Toland Jr. (1855); Mary Toland (1852-1861); Laura Tompkins (1852).
  - Subseries II.E. Rebecca Harvey Correspondence and Journal, 1848-1869; 0.31 Linear feet
    This subseries contains the correspondence and journal of Rebecca Harvey, daughter of Mary H. and Jacob Harvey, written between the years 1848 and 1869, in addition to a carte de visite depicting Rebecca Harvey. Letters from her family comprise a significant portion of the correspondence, and she received letters from her mother, Mary H. Harvey, her aunts and uncle Eliza, Sophia, and Nathaniel Hosack, as well as from Emily Hosack Rodgers and her daughter, Mary Hosack Biddle. There are a large number of letters from a Mary Isabel Rodgers, who may have been either the niece, or step-daughter, of Emily H. Rodgers. Rebecca Harvey also received letters from her relatives Mary C. Harvey and William Henry Harvey in Ireland. Correspondence, family and otherwise, is generally concerned with life and society in New York and in Ireland. Correspondents frequently reference one another, and their letters document significant events such as marriages, illnesses, and deaths, in addition to common social events, country retreats, and trips around the United States and Europe. Similarly, the journal of Rebecca Harvey is concerned with the manner in which she spends her days, her friends and acquaintances, what people wear, and social events.
    Overall, the subseries is arranged by correspondent, with documents other than correspondence situated at the end of the subseries. Correspondents represented by several letters, or who are especially notable, are arranged alphabetically and foldered by surname. Correspondents represented by three or fewer letters are foldered together.
    - Rebecca Harvey from Julia Delafield, 1860 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 5)
    - Rebecca Harvey from Mary C. Harvey, 1848 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 6)
    - Rebecca Harvey from Mary Hosack Harvey, 1862-1869, undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 7)
    - Rebecca Harvey from William Henry Harvey, 1850-1859 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 8)
    - Rebecca Harvey from Hosack Family, 1851-1857 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 9)
      Correspondents include: Eliza Hosack (1853-1856); Nathaniel Pendleton Hosack (1851-1856); Sophy Hosack (1855-1857). Additionally, an 1854 letter from Eliza Hosack to Rebecca Harvey includes newspaper clippings on the topic of the death of Bishop Wainwright.
    - Rebecca Harvey from Rodgers Family (1 of 3), 1856-1869 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 10)
      Correspondents include: Emily Hosack Rodgers (Aunt Em) (1856); Mary Hosack Biddle (Minni) (née Mary Hosack Rodgers) (1857-1869).
    - Rebecca Harvey from Mary Isabel Rodgers (2 of 3), 1851-1856 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 11)
    - Rebecca Harvey from Mary Isabel Rodgers (3 of 3), 1858-1864, undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 12)
    - Rebecca Harvey from Schermerhorn Family, 1850-1856 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 13)
      Correspondents include: Adeline Schermerhorn (Aunt Addy) (1851-1856); Ellen Schermerhorn (1850-1855).
    - Rebecca Harvey from Helen Skinner, 1855-1856 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 14)
    - Rebecca Harvey from Correspondents C-P, 1855-1857 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 15)
      Correspondents include: Mary Carter (1857); Gabrielle de Potestad (1855-1857); Julia Tillon (1855).
    - Carte de visite depicting Rebecca Harvey, undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 16)
    - Journal kept by Rebecca Harvey, 1852-1862 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 17)
  - Subseries II.F. Miscellaneous, 1819-1897; 0.08 Linear feet
    Subseries includes miscellaneous correspondence, literary efforts, and ephemera, as well as research notes compiled by the Feinses.
    The subseries is arranged first by correspondent, with documents other than correspondence appearing last.
    - Biddle Sisters Correspondence, circa 1897 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 18)
      Letters sent by the Alice McMurtrie Biddle, Constance Elizabeth Biddle, and Maria Georgina Biddle as children, from Northern France, to their mother and other correspondents.
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1828-1848 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 19)
      Correspondents include: H. Biddle to Reverend John Hughes (1848); Carew to Reuben Harvey (1846); N.H. Carter to Dr. Hosack (1828); William Henry Harvey to Hannah Todhunter (1840).
    - Notes from Unidentified, undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 20)
      Includes one loose page of notes.
    - Poetry, 1819-1830 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 21)
      Includes "The Tear" by J.E. (1819) and "The First of May" written for H.H. by W.H.H. (1830).
    - Carte de Visite Depicting Nathaniel P. Hosack, undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Hair Clippings, undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 23)
      Includes clippings from William H. Harvey and Rebecca H. Todhunter.
    - Feins Research Notes, undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 24)
      These notes had been found alongside many of the unflattened letters, but did not appear to correspond directly to any of them.
- Series III. Feins Research Notes, 1811-1994; 3 Linear feet
  This series comprises correspondence between the Feinses and various people and institutions concerning their research into the lives of Jacob Harvey and David Hosack. Also included are a prospectus for the use of the Jacob Harvey papers, the Feins's masters theses and publications, and printed matter and research notes compiled by the Feinses.
  The Feinses research notes are arranged in two subseries:
  Subseries III.A. Harvey Research Notes
  Subseries III.B. Hosack Research Notes
  - Subseries III.A. Harvey Research Notes, 1950-1994; 0.25 Linear feet
    This subseries comprises correspondence between the Feinses and various people and institutions concerning information and documents pertinent to their research into the life of Jacob Harvey. Also included are a prospectus for the use of the Jacob Harvey papers and research notes compiled by the Feinses.
    Correspondence is situated at the beginning of the subseries, followed by the prospectus for the use of the Jacob Harvey Papers and the Feinses research notes.
    - Harvey Research Correspondence, 1951-1994 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 1)
      Letters to and from various institutions and people inquiring as to the location and nature of research materials pertinant to the life and work of Jacob Harvey. Also includes letters to various publishers submitting for consideration a perspectus for the use of the Jacob Harvey papers.
    - Prospectus for the Use of the Jacob Harvey Papers, 1951 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 2)
    - Prospectus for the Use of the Jacob Harvey Papers - Carbon, 1951 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 3)
    - Prospectus Notes, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 4)
    - Research Notes (6 Folders), circa 1950 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 5-10)
  - Subseries III.B. Hosack Research Notes, 1811-1982; 2.75 Linear feet
    This subseries comprises correspondence between the Feinses and various people and institutions concerning information and documents pertinent to their research into the life of David Hosack. Also included are the Feins's masters theses and two works published by Claire Klein Feins, as well as printed matter and research notes compiled by the Feinses. Many of the folders contain typescripts prepared by Claire Feins from original materials pertaining to the life and work of David Hosack.
    Correspondence is situated at the beginning of the subseries, followed by the Feins's masters theses and publications, printed matter, and research notes.
    - Hosack Research Correspondence, 1939-1950 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 11)
      Letters to and from various institutions and people inquiring as to the location and nature of research materials pertinant to the life and work of David Hosack. Includes application materials and forms — as well as a letter of rejection — for a John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Fellowship, (1948).
    - Hosack Research Correspondence, 1947-1952 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 12)
      Letters to and from various institutions and people inquiring as to the location and nature of research materials pertinant to the life and work of David Hosack.
    - Feins Theses, undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 13)
      One bound volume comprising the masters theses of both Claire and David Feins.
    - Feins Publications. Elgin Botanic Garden Article by Claire Klein, 1939 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 14)
      Three copies of an article by Claire Feins reprinted from the December 1939 issue of the Columbia University Quaterly.
    - Feins Publications. Rockefeller Center Property Article by Claire Klein, 1941 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 15)
      Three copies of an article by Claire Feins reprinted from the February 1941 issue of the Columbia University Quaterly.
    - Research Notes. Printed Matter. 19th Century, 1811-1819 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 16)
      Two circulars from the College of Physicians and Surgeons at the University of the State of New York. These had been filed by Feinses in a folder titled "College of Physicians and Sergeons."
    - Research Notes. Printed Matter. 19th Century, 1834-1836, undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 17)
      Two copies of "A Biographical Sketch of Dr. Hosack," from the U.S. Medical and Surgical Journal (Jan. 1836); Part XIX. of The National Portrait Gallery of Distinguished Americans with portraits and essays depicting Henry Knox, David Hosack, and Francis Barber; and Emily H. Rodgers's copy of A Memoir of the Late David Hosack M.D. by His Son Alexander Eddy Hosack.
    - Research Notes. Printed Matter. Columbia University Quarterly, 1939 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 18)
    - Research Notes. Printed Matter. Journal of the Rutgers University Library, 1941 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 19)
    - Research Notes. Printed Matter. Frederick Pursh Article by Joseph Ewan, 1952 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 20)
    - Research Notes. Printed Matter. The Memoirs of William Cochran, 1954 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 21)
    - Research Notes. Printed Matter. Works by Christine Chapman Robbins, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 22)
    - Research Notes. Printed Matter. American Heritage, 1982 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 23)
    - Research Notes. Tentative Plan for a Biography of Dr. David Hosack, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 24)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Portraits, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 25)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Family of, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 26)
      Includes, among other documents, correspondence between the Feinses and the Biddle sisters. Of particular interest is one letter from Miss Alice Biddle (1962) inquiring as to the location of the Harvey Papers, and a draft of a response to her stating that her sister, Miss Constance Biddle, had left the family papers to the Feinses with the understanding that they would eventually be given to a library in New York. Also included is a Hosack Family tree written by Georgina Biddle.
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Family Record, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 27)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Manuscript of (1 of 2), circa 1950 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 28)
      Includes typescripts of manuscripts from a number of collections, including those at the New-York Historical Society, the New York Public Library, and the American Philosophical Society.
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Manuscript of (2 of 2), circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 1)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Biographies, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 2)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Historical Biographical Works, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 3)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - International Contacts, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 4)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Estimates, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 5)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - In Alexandria, Philadelphia, Social Life, Education, Death, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 6)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Pupils, Practice & Cases, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 7)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Projects, Religions, Political Views, Temperance, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 8)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Botany & Mineralogical Collection, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 9)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Lectures, Library of, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 10)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - American Philosophical Society, Royal Horticultural Society, Gifts of, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 11)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Writings by, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 12)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Writings by (2 of2), circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 13)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Ownership of Property, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 14)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Hyde Park Estate (1 of 2), circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 15)
    - Research Notes. Hosack - Hyde Park Estate. Oversize. (2 of 2), 1947 (Box OS-Small, Folder --)
      Department of the Interior Geological Survey of the Vanderbilt Mansion National Historic Site.
    - Research Notes. Hyde Park Estate (1 of 2), circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 16)
    - Research Notes. Hyde Park Estate (2 of 2), circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 17)
    - Research Notes. Elgin Botanic Garden, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 18)
      Includes an essay on the Elgin Botanic Garden, titled "Dr. Hosack's Garden," by Kenneth Andrews, printed in April 1938.
    - Research Notes. Yale University Art Gallery, Views of Elgin Garden, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 19)
      Includes photographic reproductions of sketches and paintings of Elgin Garden.
    - Research Notes. History Medical Scientific, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 20)
    - Research Notes. Humoralism, Smallpox, Treatment of Insane, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 21)
    - Research Notes. Yellow Fever, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 22)
    - Research Notes. Literary & Philosophical Socitey, Medical Education, Kappa Lambda, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 23)
    - Research Notes. Diaries & Journals & Collected Letters, circa 1950 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 24)